A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Materials, 1929-1990s; Series 10; 11.5 Linear feet Boxes 83-93, 96, 100-101
  - Fogel, Seymour (Box 93)
    - Hoffman La Roche Research Towers, Nutley, NJ, Plastic and Bas Relief Wall (1964), circa 1960s (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - I.S. 29 NYC Mosaic (1970), circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous [Includes handwritten music score by Fogel and pencil drawing], circa 1950s-1980s (Box 93, Folder 13-15)
    - Negatives, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University Phillips Hall, Ethyl Silicate (1959), circa 1950s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Post Office, Cambridge, MN (1941), circa 1940s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Primitive Music, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 19)
      Oversized materials housed in Box 101, Folder 3
    - School 383 (1977), circa 1970s (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Snapshots, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Social Security Building Mural, Washington, D.C., undated; 1984 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Unexecuted Safford U.S. Federal Bldg., AZ (1941), circa 1930s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - University Baptist Student Center, Austin, TX, undated (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Unrealized Projects, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - World's Fair [1939], circa 1938-1950s (Box 93, Folder 26)
      Oversized materials housed in Box 101, Folder 4
  - Oversized Photographs, Unidentified Artwork, [Seymour Fogel?], circa 1950s-1970s (Box 96, Folder 6-9)
    Oversized material from Box 92, Folder 15
  - Oversized Photograph, Weinman, Adolf Alexander, "Chief Black Bird", 1958 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    Oversized material from Box 91, Folder 46
  - Slides, Various Artists [Dessner (1968), Jensen, Kruskenick (1964), James Suzuki (1967), Zacharias (1968)], circa 1964-1968 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Materials housed in shoebox from Box 92, Folder 27
  - Oversized Photographs, Fogel, Seymour (Box 101)
    - Exhibitions, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 101, Folder 2)
      Oversized materials from Box 93, Folder 6
    - Primitive Music, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 101, Folder 3)
      Oversized materials from Box 93, Folder 19
    - World's Fair [1939], circa 1938-1950s (Box 101, Folder 4)
      Oversized materials from Box 93, Folder 26